Guide to the Ray Stevens Ashbery papers, [1930-1971?].
Ashbery, Ray Stevens papers, [1930-1971?].
- Series IV. Legislative files, 1949-1962 (introduction numbers).
  - 932 (Box 42, Folder 97)
  - 1030 (Box 42, Folder 98)
  - 1062 (Box 42, Folder 99)
  - 1086 (Box 42, Folder 100)
  - 1193 (Box 42, Folder 101)
  - 1196 (Box 42, Folder 102)
  - 1198 (Box 42, Folder 103)
  - 1263 (Box 42, Folder 104)
  - 1329 (Box 42, Folder 105)
  - 1331 (Box 42, Folder 106)
  - 1432 (Box 42, Folder 107)
  - 1440 (Box 42, Folder 108)
  - 1486 (Box 42, Folder 109)
  - 1499 (Box 42, Folder 110)
  - 1587 (Box 42, Folder 111)
  - 1710 (Box 42, Folder 112)
  - 1760 (Box 42, Folder 113)
  - 1814 (Box 42, Folder 114)
  - 1815 (Box 42, Folder 115)
  - 1885 (Box 42, Folder 116)
  - 1936 (Box 42, Folder 117)
  - 1996 (Box 42, Folder 118)
  - 2106 (Box 42, Folder 119)
  - 2121 (Box 42, Folder 120)
  - 2174 (Box 42, Folder 121)
  - 2247 (Box 42, Folder 122)
  - 2369 (Box 42, Folder 123)
  - 2381 (Box 42, Folder 124)
  - 2532 (Box 42, Folder 125)
  - 2540 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - 2543 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - 2604 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - 2694 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - 2717 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - 2786 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - 2810 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - 2828 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - 2838 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - 2876 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - 2903 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - 2999 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - 3005 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - 3284 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - 3303 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - 3349 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - 3376 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - 3386 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - 3425 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - 3485 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - 3517 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - 3580 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - 3610 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - 3713 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - 3714 (Box 43, Folder 25-26)
  - 3714 (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - 3837 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - 3854 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - 3864 (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - 3911 (Box 43, Folder 31-32)
  - 3927 (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - 4001 (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - 4011 (Box 43, Folder 35)
  - 4048 (Box 43, Folder 36)
  - 4059 (Box 43, Folder 37)
  - 4076 (Box 43, Folder 38)
  - 4077 (Box 43, Folder 39)
  - 4078 (Box 43, Folder 40)
  - 4155 (Box 43, Folder 41)
  - 4185 (Box 43, Folder 42-43)
  - 4186 (Box 43, Folder 44)
  - 4188 (Box 43, Folder 45)
  - 4197 (Box 43, Folder 46)
  - 4198 (Box 43, Folder 47)
  - 108 (Box 43, Folder 48)
  - 197, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 49)
  - 257 (Box 43, Folder 50)
  - 258 (Box 43, Folder 51)
  - 525 (Box 43, Folder 52)
  - 533 (Box 43, Folder 53)
  - 687 (Box 43, Folder 54)
  - 778 (Box 43, Folder 55)
  - 782 (Box 43, Folder 56)
  - 863 (Box 43, Folder 57)
  - 960 (Box 43, Folder 58)
  - 981 (Box 43, Folder 59)
  - 1048 (Box 43, Folder 60)
  - 1075 (Box 43, Folder 61)
  - 1079 (Box 43, Folder 62)
  - 1127 (Box 43, Folder 63)
  - 1347 (Box 43, Folder 64)
  - 1449 (Box 43, Folder 65)
  - 1508 (Box 43, Folder 66)
  - 1552 (Box 43, Folder 67)
  - 2010 (Box 43, Folder 68)
  - 2173 (Box 43, Folder 69)
  - 2174 (Box 43, Folder 70)
  - 2374 (Box 43, Folder 71)
  - 2375 (Box 43, Folder 72)
  - 2460 (Box 43, Folder 73)
  - 2469 (Box 43, Folder 74)
  - 2473 (Box 43, Folder 75)
  - 2679 (Box 43, Folder 76)
  - 2875 (Box 43, Folder 77)
  - 2920 (Box 43, Folder 78)
  - 2930 (Box 43, Folder 79)
  - 2931 (Box 43, Folder 80)
  - 2941 (Box 43, Folder 81)
  - 2994 (Box 43, Folder 82)
  - 3140 (Box 43, Folder 83)
  - 3287 (Box 43, Folder 84)
  - 3439 (Box 43, Folder 85)
  - 3466 (Box 43, Folder 86)
  - 3726 (Box 43, Folder 87)
  - 3834 (Box 43, Folder 88)
  - 4098 (Box 43, Folder 89)
  - 4146 (Box 43, Folder 90)
  - 4202 (Box 43, Folder 91)
  - 4226 (Box 43, Folder 92)
  - 4237 (Box 43, Folder 93)
  - 4308 (Box 43, Folder 94)
  - 4314 (Box 43, Folder 95)
  - 4321 (Box 43, Folder 96)
  - 4360 (Box 43, Folder 97)
  - 4361 (Box 43, Folder 98)
  - 4362 (Box 43, Folder 99)
  - 4368 (Box 43, Folder 100)
  - 4376 (Box 43, Folder 101)
  - 7313 (Box 43, Folder 102)
  - 9, 1959 (Box 43, Folder 103)
  - 55` (Box 43, Folder 104)
  - 127 (Box 43, Folder 105)
  - 284 (Box 43, Folder 106)
  - 305 (Box 43, Folder 107)
  - 658 (Box 43, Folder 108)
  - 870 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - 871 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - 890 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - 1039 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - 1066 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - 1151 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - 1152 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - 1327 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - 1695 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - 1796 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - 1827 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - 2201 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - 2440 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - 2706 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - 2767 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - 3075 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - 3078 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - 3157 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - 3159 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - 3395 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - 3427 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - 3615 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - 3736 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - 3737 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - 3738 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - 3844 (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - 3863 (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - 3942 (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - 4074 (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - 4095 (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - 4225 (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - 4294 (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - 4369 (Box 44, Folder 33)
  - 4371 (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - 4473 (Box 44, Folder 35)
  - 23, 1960 (Box 44, Folder 36)
  - 175 (Box 44, Folder 37)
  - 249 (Box 44, Folder 38)
  - 313 (Box 44, Folder 39)
  - 376 (Box 44, Folder 40)
  - 565 (Box 44, Folder 41)
  - 570 (Box 44, Folder 42)
  - 638 (Box 44, Folder 43)
  - 737 (Box 44, Folder 44)
  - 794 (Box 44, Folder 45)
  - 795 (Box 44, Folder 46)
  - 796 (Box 44, Folder 47)
  - 804 (Box 44, Folder 48)
  - 823 (Box 44, Folder 49)
  - 942 (Box 44, Folder 50)
  - 953 (Box 44, Folder 51)
  - 1022 (Box 44, Folder 52)
  - 1159 (Box 44, Folder 53)
  - 1295 (Box 44, Folder 54)
  - 1324 (Box 44, Folder 55)
  - 1332 (Box 44, Folder 56)
  - 1358 (Box 44, Folder 57)
  - 1474 (Box 44, Folder 58)
  - 1539 (Box 44, Folder 59)
  - 1552 (Box 44, Folder 60)
  - 1553 (Box 44, Folder 61)
  - 1648 (Box 44, Folder 62)
  - 1777 (Box 44, Folder 63)
  - 1826 (Box 44, Folder 64)
  - 1859 (Box 44, Folder 65)
  - 1920 (Box 44, Folder 66)
  - 1957 (Box 44, Folder 67)
  - 2084 (Box 44, Folder 68)
  - 2201 (Box 44, Folder 69)
  - 2249 (Box 44, Folder 70)
  - 2255 (Box 44, Folder 71)
  - 2265 (Box 44, Folder 72)
  - 2467 (Box 44, Folder 73)
  - 2704 (Box 44, Folder 74)
  - 2775 (Box 44, Folder 75)
  - 2784 (Box 44, Folder 76)
  - 2792 (Box 44, Folder 77)
  - 2865 (Box 44, Folder 78)
  - 2936 (Box 44, Folder 79)
  - 2970 (Box 44, Folder 80)
  - 3143 (Box 44, Folder 81)
  - 3188 (Box 44, Folder 82)
  - 3201 (Box 44, Folder 83)
  - 3222 (Box 44, Folder 84)
  - 3223 (Box 44, Folder 85)
  - 3231 (Box 44, Folder 86)
  - 3261 (Box 44, Folder 87)
  - 3262 (Box 44, Folder 88)
  - 3397 (Box 44, Folder 89)
  - 3422 (Box 44, Folder 90)
  - 3438 (Box 44, Folder 91)
  - 3690 (Box 44, Folder 92)
  - 3743 (Box 44, Folder 93)
  - 3755 (Box 44, Folder 94)
  - 3814 (Box 44, Folder 95)
  - 3815 (Box 44, Folder 96)
  - 3855 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - 3913 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - 3930 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - 4147 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - 4206 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - 4216 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - 4217 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - 4218 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - 4378 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - 4401 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - 4412 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - 4566 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - 4593 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - 4601 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - 4628 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - 4678 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - 4687 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - 19 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - 25 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - 62 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - 83 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - 138 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - 165 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - 181 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - 203 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - 338 (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - 347 (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - 349 (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - 445 (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - 488 (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - 566 (Box 45, Folder 31-32)
  - 568 (Box 45, Folder 33)
  - 611 (Box 45, Folder 34)
  - 730 (Box 45, Folder 35)
  - 751 (Box 45, Folder 36)
  - 812 (Box 45, Folder 37)
  - 867 (Box 45, Folder 38)
  - 868 (Box 45, Folder 39)
  - 871 (Box 45, Folder 40)
  - 937 (Box 45, Folder 41)
  - 984 (Box 45, Folder 42)
  - 988 (Box 45, Folder 43)
  - 991 (Box 45, Folder 44)
  - 993 (Box 45, Folder 45)
  - 1020 (Box 45, Folder 46)
  - 1090 (Box 45, Folder 47)
  - 1193 (Box 45, Folder 48)
  - 1418 (Box 45, Folder 49)
  - 1418 (Box 45, Folder 50)
  - 1425 (Box 45, Folder 51)
  - 1428 (Box 45, Folder 52)
  - 1438 (Box 45, Folder 53)
  - 1483 (Box 45, Folder 54-55)
  - 1488 (Box 45, Folder 56)
  - 1505 (Box 45, Folder 57)
  - 1518 (Box 45, Folder 58)
  - 1614 (Box 45, Folder 59)
  - 1664 (Box 45, Folder 60)
  - 1696 (Box 45, Folder 61)
  - 1895 (Box 45, Folder 62)
  - 1901 (Box 45, Folder 63)
  - 1910 (Box 45, Folder 64)
  - 1935 (Box 45, Folder 65)
  - 1941 (Box 45, Folder 66)
  - 2025 (Box 45, Folder 67-68)
  - 2027 (Box 45, Folder 69)
  - 2097 (Box 45, Folder 70)
  - 2121 (Box 45, Folder 71)
  - 2131 (Box 45, Folder 72)
  - 2195 (Box 45, Folder 73)
  - 2229 (Box 45, Folder 74)
  - 2340 (Box 45, Folder 75)
  - 2341 (Box 45, Folder 76)
  - 2360 (Box 45, Folder 77)
  - 2404 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - 2438 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - 2469 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - 2481 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - 2539 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - 260 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - 2713 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - 2750 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - 2753 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - 2756 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - 2867 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - 2868 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - 2888 (Box 46, Folder 13-15)
  - 2911 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - 2968 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - 3024 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - 3069 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - 3152 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - 3213 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - 3230 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - 3231 (Box 46, Folder 23-24)
  - 3290 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - 3340 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - 3418 (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - 3461 (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - 3680 (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - 3711 (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - 3712 (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - 3713 (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - 3771 (Box 46, Folder 33-34)
  - 3290 (Box 46, Folder 35)
  - 3885 (Box 46, Folder 36)
  - 4010 (Box 46, Folder 37)
  - 4073 (Box 46, Folder 38)
  - 4077 (Box 46, Folder 39)
  - 4167 (Box 46, Folder 40)
  - 4169 (Box 46, Folder 41)
  - 4201 (Box 46, Folder 42)
  - 4213 (Box 46, Folder 43)
  - 4308 (Box 46, Folder 44)
  - 4368 (Box 46, Folder 45)
  - 4464 (Box 46, Folder 46)
  - 4495 (Box 46, Folder 47-48)
  - 4540 (Box 46, Folder 49)
  - 4632 (Box 46, Folder 50)
  - 4641 (Box 46, Folder 51-53)
  - 4642 (Box 46, Folder 54)
  - 4644 (Box 46, Folder 55-56)
  - 4646 (Box 46, Folder 57)
  - 4651 (Box 46, Folder 58)
  - 4654 (Box 46, Folder 59-60)
  - 4655 (Box 46, Folder 61-62)
  - 4657 (Box 46, Folder 63)
  - 4788 (Box 46, Folder 64)
  - 4918 (Box 46, Folder 65)
  - 4982 (Box 46, Folder 66)
  - 10 (Box 46, Folder 67)
  - 102, 1962 (Box 46, Folder 68)
  - 135 (Box 46, Folder 69)
  - 145 (Box 46, Folder 70)
  - 146 (Box 46, Folder 71)
  - 163 (Box 46, Folder 72)
  - 203 (Box 46, Folder 73)
  - 256 (Box 46, Folder 74)
  - 262 (Box 46, Folder 75)
  - 356 (Box 46, Folder 76)
  - 357 (Box 46, Folder 77)
  - 395 (Box 46, Folder 78)
  - 445 (Box 46, Folder 79)
  - 457 (Box 46, Folder 80)
  - 462 (Box 46, Folder 81)
  - 513 (Box 46, Folder 82)
  - 527 (Box 46, Folder 83)
  - 531 (Box 46, Folder 84)
  - 545 (Box 46, Folder 85)
  - 556 (Box 46, Folder 86)
  - 559 (Box 46, Folder 87)
  - 564 (Box 46, Folder 88)
  - 578 (Box 46, Folder 89)
  - 612 (Box 46, Folder 90)
  - 617 (Box 46, Folder 91)
  - 642 (Box 46, Folder 92)
  - 643 (Box 46, Folder 93)
  - 692 (Box 46, Folder 94)
  - 697 (Box 46, Folder 95)
  - 763 (Box 46, Folder 96)
  - 770 (Box 46, Folder 97)
  - 778 (Box 46, Folder 98)
  - 856 (Box 46, Folder 99)
  - 867 (Box 46, Folder 100)
  - 905 (Box 46, Folder 101)
  - 1032 (Box 46, Folder 102)
  - 1038 (Box 46, Folder 103)
  - 1076 (Box 46, Folder 104)
  - 1077 (Box 46, Folder 105)
  - 1179 (Box 46, Folder 106)
  - 1233 (Box 46, Folder 107)
  - 1233 (Box 46, Folder 108)
  - 1346 (Box 46, Folder 109)
  - 1393 (Box 46, Folder 110)
  - 1490 (Box 46, Folder 111)
  - 1580 (Box 46, Folder 112)
  - 1582 (Box 46, Folder 113)
  - 1583 (Box 46, Folder 114)
  - 1584 (Box 46, Folder 115)
  - 1585 (Box 46, Folder 116)
  - 1586 (Box 46, Folder 117)
  - 1587 (Box 46, Folder 118)
  - 1589 (Box 46, Folder 119)
  - 1611 (Box 46, Folder 120)
  - 1675 (Box 46, Folder 121)
  - 1676 (Box 46, Folder 122)
  - 1711 (Box 46, Folder 123)
  - 1730 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - 1734 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - 1745 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - 1796 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - 1825 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - 1875 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - 1936 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - 1970 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - 2074 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - 2093 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - 2096 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - 2103 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - 2180 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - 2234 (Box 47, Folder 14-15)
  - 2471 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - 2510 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - 2534 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - 2535 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - 2537 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - 2538 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - 2545 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - 2609 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - 2635 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - 2740 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - 2819 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - 2832 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - 2839 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - 2843 (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - 2959 (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - 2960 (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - 2975 (Box 47, Folder 32)
  - 3051 (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - 3052 (Box 47, Folder 34)
  - 3056 (Box 47, Folder 35)
  - 3060 (Box 47, Folder 36)
  - 3076 (Box 47, Folder 37)
  - 3077 (Box 47, Folder 38)
  - 3157 (Box 47, Folder 39)
  - 3268 (Box 47, Folder 40)
  - 3333 (Box 47, Folder 41)
  - 3336 (Box 47, Folder 42)
  - 3408 (Box 47, Folder 43)
  - 3545 (Box 47, Folder 44)
  - 3576 (Box 47, Folder 45)
  - 3582 (Box 47, Folder 46)
  - 3605 (Box 47, Folder 47)
  - 3606 (Box 47, Folder 48)
  - 3688 (Box 47, Folder 49)
  - 3747 (Box 47, Folder 50)
  - 3778 (Box 47, Folder 51)
  - 3861 (Box 47, Folder 52)
  - 3926 (Box 47, Folder 53)
  - 3927 (Box 47, Folder 54)
  - 4089 (Box 47, Folder 55)
  - 4112 (Box 47, Folder 56)
  - 4121 (Box 47, Folder 57)
  - 4137 (Box 47, Folder 58)
  - 4179 (Box 47, Folder 59)
  - 4234 (Box 47, Folder 60)
  - 4318 (Box 47, Folder 61)
  - 4344 (Box 47, Folder 62)
  - 4353 (Box 47, Folder 63)
  - 4571 (Box 47, Folder 64)
  - 4636 (Box 47, Folder 65)
  - 4795 (Box 47, Folder 66)
  - 4797 (Box 47, Folder 67)
  - 4798 (Box 47, Folder 68)
  - 4799 (Box 47, Folder 69)
  - 4800 (Box 47, Folder 70)
  - 4801 (Box 47, Folder 71)
  - 4868 (Box 47, Folder 72)
  - 48786 (Box 47, Folder 73)
  - 4913 (Box 47, Folder 74)
  - 4979 (Box 47, Folder 75)
  - 5039 (Box 47, Folder 76)
  - 5122 (Box 47, Folder 77)
  - 5123 (Box 47, Folder 78)
  - 5126 (Box 47, Folder 79)
  - 5149 (Box 47, Folder 80)
  - 2531, 1949 (Box 47, Folder 81)
  - 737, 1950 (Box 47, Folder 82)
  - 2118 (Box 47, Folder 83)
  - 160, 1951 (Box 47, Folder 84)
  - 196 (Box 47, Folder 85)
  - 197 (Box 47, Folder 86)
  - 2781 (Box 47, Folder 87)
  - 1399, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 88)
  - 2075 (Box 47, Folder 89)
  - 2117 (Box 47, Folder 90)
  - 988, 1953 (Box 47, Folder 91)
  - 2850 (Box 47, Folder 92)
  - 736, 1954 (Box 47, Folder 93)
  - 963 (Box 47, Folder 94)
  - 1041 (Box 47, Folder 95)
  - 1789 (Box 47, Folder 96)
  - 2812 (Box 47, Folder 97)
  - 42, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 98)
  - 1165 (Box 47, Folder 99)
  - 3039, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 100)
  - 43, 1956 (Box 47, Folder 101)
  - 1033 (Box 47, Folder 102)
  - 2432 (Box 47, Folder 103)
  - 3166, 1957 (Box 47, Folder 104)
  - 3526 (Box 47, Folder 105)
  - 2956, 1958 (Box 47, Folder 106)
  - 3582, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 107)
  - 875, 1961 (Box 47, Folder 108)
  - 1200 (Box 47, Folder 109)
  - 3807 (Box 47, Folder 110)